<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Privacy on Savvas Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/privacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Privacy on Savvas Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:06:18 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Which Browser i am using and why</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/which-browser-i-am-using-and-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:06:18 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/which-browser-i-am-using-and-why/</guid>
      <description>After conducting extensive research on internet browsers over the past four years, I aim to elucidate which browser I believe is optimal for the average user and provide reasons for my recommendation. Please note that this is solely my personal opinion, and it may not necessarily be universally applicable.&#xA;The browser I advocate for is Brave. Below, I will analyze and elucidate my choice, explaining why I endorse Brave.&#xA;Brave stands out initially as a browser that functions seamlessly upon installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Privacy and Security Matters</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/why-privacy-and-security-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 13:05:18 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/why-privacy-and-security-matters/</guid>
      <description>We live in the modern age of didital data exploitation. Big tech companies are trying to make big profits from users data and targeted-advertising. Our privacy and security is at a critical stage and everyone shall try to be more alerted of what information are exposing to the web. For starters, let me explain the difference between privacy and security from my prespective.&#xA;Privacy is the assurance that your data is only seen by the parties you itent to view it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
